大家好
我是小五
今天和大家一同观赏的是
2015年世界羽毛球锦标赛男单半决赛
由中国选手陈龙对阵日本选手桃田贤斗
第一局一比一龙控网抓桃田的推挑劈杀
斜线得分
三比一龙推挑过顶往前分斜线
陶推挑过顶往前连续逼压龙控正手网
前分斜线龙回搓高质量龙
半场杀球得分
Well
Ten wrong wasn't quite sure
When he should have left it
But it was such a short left you might as well
Give it up thump
Yeah
Exactly
No no point in taking any chances
No one can turn
五比一
龙推挑头顶
桃下压龙接杀分
对角龙控网逃快推
拉开龙
反拍过渡斜线龙下压放网逃快推转身龙
高质量反拍过度
桃分球抢攻
龙防守反击得分
二比六好抓推
上网跟进逃
劈掉斜线龙
放远网
抓推拦截得分
Nice
Maybe at the moment mamoto
The whole occasion uh
七比二
龙推挑过顶陶
连续控正手
抓过度进攻
龙连续反拍扑压得分
As proving in that look at that back and smash
Follows up
He's got such a physical
九比二掏空往下压龙接杀分
对角逃控正手抓摆脱进攻
中路追身得分
12比四逃控转身
双方网前较量
讨假动作
分球下压推扑弹网得分
First time the lucky neck cord for cter monala
He's got a certain
Sort of horror about him
As a certain star quality
Yeah
Ui totally agree
He looks really composed on court
Even though he's got to start like this
五比12龙甲动作分球正手杀一拍好抓推
In the chen long shot
龙控转身放网逃反控正手
双方网前较量
操控正手抓过度下压
陶抓推
高点分球龙控头顶抓
摆脱下压
陶廷顿逼起球
起跳杀一拍往前钓鱼
逼起球淘杀
上网连贯得分
My goodness
How hard
Swell when you when you said
Everything
You know chen ong
Just nullifies things
I was watching specifically in that rally
He doesn't just nullify it
He gets it back with interest half the time
It's amazing
六比12龙控正手
双方网前较量好下压推头顶龙下压逃挡网
摆脱推扑龙反顶
后场实现反杀
Good
How quick is that
But
14比六龙抓推上网跟进
抓扑得分
Fifteen six
15比六
逃控转身龙斜线过渡
逃控正手
陶连续控两底线
龙推挑过顶抓过度
侧身突击一拍上网快推斜线得分
Smash straight down the line there
It is
And look how he follows up
19比八逃网前对角变化下压高点分斜线得分
20比九调控转身往前
连续逼压逃控转身
但过度失误
龙赢得了首局比赛的胜利
but i Hope应该from the motup
But all credit to chen long
Because his steam peterson was saying
I think that's probably
The best
We've seen him more toilet
第二局四比一双方网前较量
淘下压放网下压上网跟进龙高质量推挑
使陶判断失误六比五
龙甲动作分球
逃反勾对角
逃往前分斜线
龙回搓陶推
挑过顶
龙网前分斜斜好推挑过顶
双方斗网陶推挑过顶
往前对角变化
半场杀球得分
Serve the soover six all well
I notice both men at one stage in that rally
Having to neutralize their opponents
by7平龙甲动作
分球跑
推挑过顶放网龙推头顶朝下压推
转身龙反拍过渡
逃网前对角变化
逃空网抢攻得分
九比八龙控头顶朝下压
快推转身龙反拍过渡龙
高质量推斜线
使陶判断失误
十比九龙下压上网跟进
陶连续控转身
放网龙
停顿逼起球
头顶突击直线得分
Even
Strong movement to get behind the shuttle
And because he's imbalance and
Control of his movements
Able to sweat the shuttle down the line look at that
11比九龙控头顶朝下压龙抓推突击得分
Oh he was really looking for a push down the forehand side there
Wasn't he
Yeah
He totally read that well
Nine was waiting out there
And i think we needs to have a little bit
More disguises from the front court
Memortto
11比15淘下压龙空网抢攻
上网跟进
龙抓推陶鱼跃救球
网前高质量回扣得分
What retrieving from por mamorta
Get back a magnificent
Now think it's up to
And look at his night
Shot that is perfection
Absolutely amazing
Look at this upbegets
And then the control on the next shot
13比15淘沙上网连贯得分好的
He's really hold from pushes
But that will help when he does want to push it
15比16龙停顿
逼起球
头顶进攻
追身得分
17比15
掏空网抢攻
上网跟进
劈掉斜线
龙放网头顶突击一拍
双方网前较量
陶推挑过顶放网控转身
龙回缩
高质量
龙莎上网连贯得分
Kill up the ne that one
He just lifted perhaps the tumble
And spin of the shuttle was too vicious for him to take it
Early
He best rally on the pl
19比15龙推挑过顶
双方网前较量调控转身
龙控正手
双方圆网控制龙分球抢攻得分
Oh he's on the roll is chen rock
Look at him wins
The rally in jokes back
And in second message to the two players in the next seven pes
Yeah
You gotta be on top of that game to have a chance against the name
The final
Look how early is taking up on it
He was following up to have come back
20比15
龙控头顶朝下压上网跟进淘侧身杀一拍
双方网前较量
陶推挑过顶放网龙控网抢攻终结比赛
以大比分二比零战胜日本选手桃田贤斗
闯入2015年世界羽毛球锦标赛男单决赛
Of china will contest the final once again
Fifty two minutes of dominant swey
There was only a short spell where i really thought the motor
Had a chance
But sensing the pressure
This man chin wrong
Just stop the intensity
No water performance
So i think steam
Peterson was absolutely right
When he said
And that perhaps that water final uh
Against another seventeen victor
Axelson in the second game where chen long in all honesty
Looked a little bit wobbly victor absence
And wasn't forced playing very well
But twin thirty
Twenty nine in that quarter final
And that tough match perhaps
Sharpened him for today's semi final uh
Because rap was exactly
Yep
And he's pleased with that
And so you should be
The depending champion
Chen long cl to the final once again
Twenty one nine
Twenty one fifteen in fifty two minutes